Register of the Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty broadcast records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Romanian Broadcasting Department Records, 1959-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings, editor's files, and scripts. In process. Target regions include Romania and Moldova. Languages include Romanian. The Romanian Broadcasting Department began Moldova-specific programming in 1998 and ceased programming to Romania in 2008. For Romanian language content from 2008-present, see the Moldovan Service Records. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Romanian Broadcasting Department Records
- Russian Service Records, 1953-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings, editor's files, and scripts. In process. Also known as Russian Broadcasting Department, Radio Svoboda. Target regions include Russia and former Soviet republics. Languages include Russian. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Access to RFE/RL Russian Service sound recordings is handled by the Vera and Donald Blinken Open Society Archives (OSA). They have a fully-searchable database available on their website at http://www.osaarchivum.org/digital-repository
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Russian Service Records
- Slovak Service Records, 1993-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings, editor's files, and scripts. In process. Target regions include Slovakia. Languages include Slovak. The Czechoslovak Broadcasting Department split into the Czech and Slovak services in 1993; for Slovak language content prior to 1993, see the Czechoslovak Broadcasting Department Records. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2004 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Slovak Service Records
- South Slavic Service (Balkan Service) Records, 1969-2013 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings. In process. Also known as Albanian Service, Balkan Service, and South Slavic and Albanian service. Target regions include Albania, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Kosovo, Macedonia, Montenegro and Serbia. Languages include Albanian, Bosnian, Croatian, Macedonian, Montenegrin, and Serbian. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the South Slavic Service (Balkan Service) Records
- Tajik Service Records, 1970-2013 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings. In process. Also known as Radio Ozodi. Target regions include Tajikistan. Languages include Tajik. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Tajik Service Records
- Tatar-Bashkir Service Records, 1952-2007 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings, editor's files, and scripts. Also known as Radio Azatliq. Target regions include Bashkortostan, Tatarstan, and Ukraine. Languages include Bashkir, Crimean Tatar, and Tatar. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Tatar-Bashkir Service Records
- Turkmen Service Records, 1988-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings. In process. Also known as Radio Azatlyk. Target regions include Turkmenistan. Languages include Turkmen. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Turkmen Service Records
- Ukrainian Service Records, 1952-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings, editor's files, and scripts. In process. Also known as Radio Svoboda. Target regions include Ukraine. Languages include Ukrainian, Russian, and Crimean Tatar. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006 and Daily Broadcast Analyses for brief descriptions of topics covered during broadcasts.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Ukrainian Service Records
- Uzbek Service Records, 1987-1995 (On-shelf shelf)
  Sound recordings. In process. Also known as Radio Ozodlik. Target regions include Uzbekistan. Languages include Uzbek. See also Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings for recordings from 1995-2006.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Uzbek Service Records
- Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings, 1960-2006 (On-shelf shelf)
  Services include Armenian, Azerbaijani, Belarusian, Bulgarian, Czech, Estonian, Georgian, Kazakh, Kyrgyz, Latvian, Lithuanian, North Caucasus, Persian (Radio Azadi, Radio Farda), Polish, Radio Free Afghanistan (Radio Azadi), Radio Free Iraq, Radio Marshaal, Romanian, Russian, Slovak, South Slavic (Balkan), Tajik, Tatar-Bashkir, Turkmen, Ukrainian, and Uzbek. In process.
  Downloadable PDF inventory of the Multiple Language Services Sound Recordings